same Uncle Joe he's going to an already
bigger this way okay so why put some put
something in the air and sanded push up
in the air rocket yeah well for a start
you your world is here then you thought
I could get rid of that nice black
and grind it up Oh over there and if you
sent them don't we play a game process
looks really nice if it was forget
therefore what do you see them yo your
brown where's this oughta gonna go
where's it playing again inside looks
nice Andy that's up but on the inside
have a look all the way through the top
everybody the inside had had cells had
that water had needed to get it I don't
want to look for you now it's already
resting up and stainless to Russ real
good stainless to ruston doesn't do that
is that going to carry a positive charge
and the sellers or just a headache it's
all I to be negative yeah I put party
with charges so what are you going to
happen here and there you go sees you
just gonna like it
that is not stainless anymore stainless
is what stay nice we're trying to get
what we call this now stain stain steel
somebody cut at somebody well that
somebody finds he did up somebody
changed it somebody grounded somebody
somebody the outside has been done boy
okay okay that will do is bend unbind
okay and the Peters not in easy okay
okay and somebody is sanded the inside
and this piece here is on the waist
waist side of not the milks a food-grade
rock sided so it was on the lake side
and they tried to clean that up on the
inside it will look nice on the outside
mm-hmm okay again should ask me inside
and then around here to bring that down
in there any girl sees here well WP hold
up the camera that's back with you come
even if this church were below that okay
even if they were below that knew any
girls the energy like you want coming up
there will not pass that point
this awesome oh the stainless keeps
memory yes sir working that's the worst
I had a battle for me to see water keeps
memory placed it keeps memory ever seen
the toys that they're making out of play
sticks in metal and everything else they
put memory into the place T this might
look like a bottle here now and you just
put it fold it into some other shape and
so on like that might make it look like
a horse in these metals or plastics and
they give it to kids okay for toys so
they molded in a different shape and
then another show you another shape and
how do you bring that back into looking
like a bottle it's got the memory they
either put it into the fridge or they
put into the you know the oven or now
you just eat it up or they could order
over to do many other things to bring
different temperatures to it and it will
have the memory of every single thing
that you've formed out and it'll just
make each one again boy how that warmth
orbital cold or anything else to bring
it back into memory that happens with
place dixon happens with medicine eric
they're going to be all cars out of this
so that you have a deep don't need a
paddle better because you have it didn't
everything else you just drive your car
in there for a little bit of warmth or
something colder water whatever they
require to be no your mouth guards back
out to what it used to be you are your
cars back in shape it's not very
productive
what about metal they've found a problem
scrunch it up good show Rebecca
understand how much you go to the German
aluminium at the present moment without
discussing all those things in the
aluminium is like butter I'm covered the
aluminium is like butter and you can put
a pic thread into it put the biggest
fattest hi tents are bold into it right
you cut it with a butter knife and you
thread this read into it you put a high
tensile bolt into it get you get the
biggest longer swimming pool bar socket
on to it I've done it and I've had both
feet on the side of the bench put follow
me home you gotta hedge book okay not
pulling like man I never you go on you
know broke don't like tuna boat gulping
I didn't pull this ready I'm bringing
rachel on been to my poor now I'm gonna
have to hit the road garota okay bit
messy happy and so on for the boat yep
so they've got that and you can just
slice of the gutter but you can't pull
it through but then once you broke it
off you don't how do you get the thread
yeah the broken off both ready to touch
your finger on it put your finger in
there sit on top of the breakup I've
ever turning it from wine without the
damn thing comes back out so she helps
them in their ear I don't worry I'll
releasing in the mirror you guys for
think of that but we're not talking man
so I'm going to have to leave use and
you just talk on the play on video
unaware Elspeth your self analyzing of
those things should be telling you now
exactly what you meant yeah exactly what
you shouldn't be doing and then using
the head on how to get away from that to
come up with what you got because the
north coast and what's up being welded
brought in and all these things has been
unist doesn't break down doesn't magnet
or something stuff down across three but
can't figure out how they do you don't
know what that formal wildung is called
if I do that's just evil no you will oh
I'm 80 so y'all don't know Carolyn to my
vanity some of you I'm not an oak alley
in fig roll with you yeah um I don't
want to tell you how I to office
material thank you sure that's all right
Benjamin would have loved it up here
yeah thank you while he's gone